Peggy L. Chinn Papers
© 2009 University of Connecticut
Peggy L. Chinn Papers.
undated, 1969-2003
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Chinn, Peggy L.
3.1 linear feet.
Professional papers of Peggy Chinn, emerita Professor of Nursing at the University of Connecticut.
MSS20080099
Biography
Author, editor, instructor and registered nurse, Peggy Chinn was a Professor of Nursing and the University of Connecticut from January 1997 until her retirement in June 2003. Details of Dr. Chinn's interests, activities and current vita is available from her website.
Scope and Contents
Arrangement
The materials are listed as received from the donor but have been reboxed and serials removed for cataloging.
Box Inventory ( undated, 1969-2003 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to nursing history and education in Connecticut. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Cassandra: Radical Feminist Nurses Network Dodd Periodicals
Theory and Nursing. Integrated Knowledge Development Dodd
Art & Aesthetics in Nursing Dodd
Peace & Power. A Handbook of Feminist Process, 2nd and 3rd eds. Dodd
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Chinn, Peggy L.
Subjects:
Nursing.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Publications.; Photographs.; Administrative Records.; Audio visual materials.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Manuscripts.; Photocopies.; Notes.; Drawings.; Speeches.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
Acquisition Information
Detailed Description
- Box Inventory, undated
  - (Box 1)
    - Heide, Wilma Scott, 1984-1986
    - Letters from Wilma, undated, 1978-1985
    - Reviews, 1985-1986
    - American Journal of Nursing anniversary issue, 1975
    - Nursing history research, undated
    - Promotional comments, 1985
    - Photographs (Wilma?), undated
    - Schutt, Barbara, 1986
    - Samples, undated, 1986
    - Bernard, Jessie, 1987
    - Moon symbols, undated
    - Sheroes Evaluations, 1986-1987
    - Heide, Wilma Scott Speeches and articles, undated, 1969-1973
    - Heide, Wilma Scott correspondence, undated, 1972
    - Cassandra: Radical Feminist Nurses Network flyer, undated
    - Cartoons, undated
    - Revision letter agreement, 2003
    - Healing Music, 1994-1998
    - Wholistic Modalities, 1991-1998
    - WebCT and HTML, 2001-2003
    - Nurse Manifest, 2003
    - Gossip, 1993
    - History, undated
    - Nightingale, undated
    - Feminism, undated
    - Oermann chapters, 2002
    - Sophia: Footbinder, undated
    - Feminist Analysis Guide, undated, 1984
    - Nurse Manifest Study, 2003
    - Friendship Survey, 1986-1995
    - Songs/Chants, undated
    - Lesbian Nurses Network, 1998
    - Hawaii, 2003
    - April Lecture, 2002
    - ENRS Website, 2002
    - Reject Thank yous, 1996
    - Advances in Nursing Science manuscript articles, undated
  - (Box 2)
    - School of Nursing and Web how to, 2001
    - Advances in Nursing Science, undated, 1978-1985
    - Friendship Study, undated
    - Pie chart overheads, undated
    - AJN Questionnaire overheads, undated
    - Woman's Day survey overheads, undated
    - Family Circle survey overheads, undated
    - Art study, undated
    - Advances in Nursing Science manuscript articles, undated
    - Tatum, Peggy, undated
    - Charlene, undated
    - PLC drawings and photographs, undated
    - Comments (Correspondence), 1987
    - PLC photographs, undated
    - National League for Nursing, 1992
    - CEUs, 1991-1993
    - Amazing letters (correspondence), 1995-1998
    - Photographs, undated
    - Wright State University School of Nursing presentation, 1980
    - Advances in Nursing Science initial agreements, 1977-1979
    - Lesbian Nurse History Project, undated
    - Advances in Nursing Science, undated
    - Friendship Study, undated
    - Summer Project, 2001
    - Criticism Study, undated
  - (Box 3)
    - Research, articles and correspondence, undated, 1990
    - Research, undated
    - Degrees and awards, 1970-1999
    - CD of Photographs, undated, 1992-1996